<application>
  <component name="AppStorage">
    <histories>
      <item value="integritycheck" />
      <item value="integrity" />
      <item value="he Throwable class is the superclass of all errors and exceptions in the Java language. Only objects that are instances of this class (or one of its subclasses) are thrown by the Java Virtual Machine or can be thrown by the Java throw statement. Similarly, only this class or one of its subclasses can be the argument type in a catch clause. For the purposes of compile-time checking of exceptions, Throwable and any subclass of Throwable that is not also a subclass of either RuntimeException or Error are regarded as checked exceptions. Instances of two subclasses, Error and Exception, are conventionally used to indicate that exceptional situations have occurred. Typically, these instances are freshly created in the context of the exceptional situation so as to include relevant information (such as stack trace data). A throwable contains a snapshot of the execution stack of its thread at the time it was created. It can also contain a message string that gives more information about the error. Over time, a throwable can suppress other throwables from being propagated. Finally, the throwable can also contain a cause: another throwable that caused this throwable to be constructed. The recording of this causal information is referred to as the chained exception facility, as the cause can, itself, have a cause, and so on, leading to a &quot;chain&quot; of exceptions, each caused by another. One reason that a throwable may have a cause is that the class that throws it is built atop a lower layered abstraction, and an operation on the upper layer fails due to a failure in the lower layer. It would be bad design to let the throwable thrown by the lower layer propagate outward, as it is generally unrelated to the abstraction provided by the upper layer. Further, doing so would tie the API of the upper layer to the details of its implementation, assuming the lower layer's exception was a checked" />
      <item value="检查发布状态" />
      <item value="quota" />
      <item value="Rectangle of underlying button, relative to the overlay's dimensions." />
      <item value="stroke Width" />
      <item value="positional" />
      <item value="flat" />
      <item value="Refactor" />
      <item value="Decoration" />
      <item value="P 151_Reverse Words In A String" />
      <item value="String" />
      <item value="reverse Words" />
      <item value="like" />
      <item value="not" />
      <item value="hello" />
      <item value="输入：&quot;  hello world!  &quot;" />
      <item value="blue" />
    </histories>
    <option name="languageScores">
      <map>
        <entry key="CHINESE" value="12" />
        <entry key="ENGLISH" value="13" />
        <entry key="ITALIAN" value="1" />
      </map>
    </option>
  </component>
  <component name="Cache">
    <option name="lastTrimTime" value="1623054165227" />
  </component>
  <component name="Settings">
    <option name="googleTranslateSettings">
      <google-translate>
        <option name="useTranslateGoogleCom" value="true" />
      </google-translate>
    </option>
  </component>
</application>